Finding Aid for the Edward East Barthell Lantern Slide Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Slides 592-615
  - Iconography/Art
    - Emile Verhaeren (French author) (Box 31)
    - Statue (Box 31)
    - Edmond Rostand (French writer) (Box 31)
    - Henri Bergson (French philosopher) (Box 31)
    - Rodin (French sculptor) (Box 31)
    - Bay of Naples & Vesuvius (Box 31)
    - Avenue of Trees – Hobbema (Box 31)
    - Baptism, Life of Our Lord (Box 31)
    - Madonna – Cimabue (Box 31)
    - Landscape – Corot (Box 31)
    - The Holy Night – Correggio (Box 31)
    - Dignity & Impudence - Landseer (Box 31)
    - Immaculate Conception – Murillo (Box 31)
    - Christ’s Charge to Peter – Raphael (Box 31)
    - Sistine Madonna – Raphael (Box 31)
    - Figures from Anatomy Lesson – Rembrandt (Box 31)
    - Age of Innocence – Reynolds (Box 31)
    - The Cherub Choir – Reynolds (Box 31)
    - Adoration of the Shepherds – Tissot (Box 31)
    - Madonna of the Rabbit – Titian (Box 31)
    - Whistler’s Mother – Whistler (Box 31)
    - Descent from the Cross – Willink (Box 31)
    - Unidentified (Box 31)
    - Sistine Madonna – Raphael (Box 31)